太好了  大家都在
Good, you guys are all here!
怎么了
Hey! What's up?
我明天要去拉夫·劳伦公司面试
Well, I have a job interview at Ralph Lauren tomorrow!
恭喜  太棒了
Congratulations! Ohh, that's great!
那个牌子的内裤好差劲
Boy, that guy's underwear sucks!
什么
Wh-what?!
我买了一条超大号内裤(其实是XS 特小号)
I got this pair marked excess,
里头根本塞不下多余的东西
I gotta tell ya, there was no room for excess anything in there.
总之  工作是女装部协调员
Anyway, I'm going to be the coordinator of the woman's collection,
我直接在主管底下做事
I'll work right under the director,
这是我梦寐以求的工作
it's the perfect, perfect job for me!
-只要通过面试就行了  -是啊
- Wow! Well, if you nail the interview, you'll get it! - Yeah.
-要不要练习一下面试技巧  -好的
- You wanna work on your interview skills? - O-okay!
来  先从握手开始
Okay! All right, let's start with the handshake.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
很会握  手腕的动作很棒
Very good handshake, good wrist action.
-我来试试  -好
- Let me try. - Okay.
天啊  我是哪里对不起你了
Oh my God! What did I ever do to you?!
我握得太用力了吗
Did I squeeze it too hard?
这么说吧  好在我不是钱德勒
Let's just say, I'm glad I'm not Chandler.
罗斯  我能看到你在新公寓
That's right Ross, I can see you in your new apartment!
你也看得到我
And you can see me!
跟昨天一样  跟前天也一样
Same as yesterday,  same as the day before.
他开始演鲨鱼攻击了没
Is he doing his shark attack bit yet?
还没  等等  开始了
Nope. Op, wait! There he goes.
罗斯  很好笑
Very funny Ross!
栩栩如生又好笑
Very life-like and funny. Okay.
不  小姐  我不是向你挥手
Oh no-no-no, I wasn't waving at you lady.
或许我是哦
Whoa, maybe I was!
莫妮卡  罗斯那栋楼里
Hey, Monica, this totally hot girl
有个辣妹在勾引我
in Ross's building is flirting with me.
上吧  勾引回来  瞎搅和
Get in there man! Flirt back, mix it up!
我同意
Yeah, I-I-I'm down with that.
好  开始吧
Okay, here goes.
你  好  吗
How  you  a-doin'?
有用  她在向我挥手
It worked! She's waving me over.
我马上过去  我看看  她住在三楼
Okay, I-I-I'll be right over. Let's see, she's on the third floor...
她真的很漂亮
Wow! She is pretty, huh?
这还用你说
Tell me about it, huh?
不  我跟她没关系
Oh no-no-no, I'm not with her,
她只是莫妮卡
that's just Monica!
乔伊  我很会演吧
Hey Joey! Great stuff huh?
这是你家
This is your place?
当然是  请进
Of course it is. Yeah, come on in.
对了  在窗户边可以假装在冲浪
Ooh-ooh, go by the window you can pretend to be surfing.
可是我数过啊
But I counted,
这里住的不应该是你  要命
you're not supposed to live here! Oh man!
怎么了
What happened?
我跑到罗斯家去了
I ended up at Ross's place.
我一定是数错了
Oh, I must missed counted or something.
可恶  她不在了
Damn! She's not there anymore.
你看  罗斯在演"看电视"那段
Oh, l-l-look, Ross is doing his 'Watching TV' bit.
乔伊  我觉得他真的在看电视
No Joey, I think he's just watchin' TV.
嫌犯已失去踪迹
We've lost visual contact with the suspect.
好了  我现在非走不可了
Okay, now I've really have to go!
这真是太不公平了  我们的约会被中断
But it's just so unfair that our date has to get cut short
就因为有人开枪打了店员
just 'cause some guy shot at a store clerk.
亲爱的  我知道  但这是我的工作
I know, but it's my job, sweethart!
不如我一起去
Okay, then maybe I can come too!
嫌犯刚从下水道中裸体现身
Suspect has just emerged naked from the sewer.
好吧  你去就好
All right, you go.
-再见  -再见
- Bye bye. - Okay, bye bye.
天啊
Oh God!
怎么了
What?
我好想他
Oh I just miss him so much!
才一星期就这么甜蜜啦
For just a week you guys are really close, huh?
是啊  说来很奇怪
Yeah, it's weird.
可是我没办法  他真的很体贴
I can't help it though he's so sweet,
像是小狗狗
he's like this little puppy dog, y'know?
却很强悍  还会开枪打坏人
But like a really tough one that shots bad guys.
我好喜欢刚开始恋爱的感觉
Ohh, I just love beginning parts of relationships, y'know?!
彼此难分难舍
You just like can't keep your hands off each other.
我知道  热恋是最棒的
I know it is the best.
你和钱德勒的热恋持续了多久
So-so how long did that last for you and Chandler?
什么  我们还在热恋啊
What? It's still going on.
少来  说真的  何时结束的
Come on, seriously! When did it end?
我是说真的  我们总是粘在一起
I-I am serious, I mean, we're, we're all over each other all the time.
好吧  你们的事你最清楚
Okay, you know where you are better than I do.
我只是好奇罢了
I was just curious.
菲比  你别发神经了好不好
What don't you just calm down Phoebe! All right?!
请你先去把事实搞清楚
Why don't you just get all your facts before you run around
再宣布全天下只有你们在热恋
telling everybody that you're the only hot couple!!
天啊  把野兽唤醒了
God, I woke the beast.
显然是我错了  我失言了  没事了
I was wrong obviously, I just-I misspoke. It's okay.
没关系  你知道就行
Oh no, it is okay, I mean as long as you know that
我和钱德勒  也和你们一样火热缠绵
Chandler and I are also very hot and fiery, just as hot as you!
我们的欲火简直可以燎原
I mean our flame, whew, is on fire!
莫妮卡  扫把还你
Hey Monica, here's your broom back.
你真可爱
You are so cute.
面试顺不顺利
Oh hey, how'd the interview go?
糟透了
Ugh, horrible!
我犯了最蠢最丢人的错误
I did the stupidest, most embarrassing thing!
你跟面试官说要跟他老婆上床
Did you tell the guy you wanted to have sex with his wife
然后又从椅子上跌下来吗
and then fall right out of your chair?
不是
No!
那是怎么了
So what happened?
真是糟糕透顶
Ugh, it was horrible!
原本面试很顺利
And-and the interview part went so well, y'know?
我还把他逗笑了
I even made him laugh.
面试官说到什么船的事  我答腔说
He said something about a boat and I was like,
"是啊  只要救生衣够多就行"
"Well, yeah! If you've got enough life jackets!"
相信我  当时真的很逗
Trust me, it was actually, it was very funny.
总之  到了最后说再见时
Anyway, so we were saying good-bye and ugh!
怎么了
What happened?
我们当时正要握手  他缓缓朝我靠过来
All right, we were shaking hands and he kinda leaned toward me...
他也许是要帮我开门
Y'know maybe he was going to open the door,
但是我完全误会了  所以我就
but I totally miss read him and I uhhh...
你亲了上去
You kissed him?!
我不知道该做些什么
Well, I didn't know what else to do!
你可以试着  别去亲他
Well you coulda tried, not kissing him.
钱德勒  真是多谢你
Thanks Chandler.
瑞秋  拉夫·劳伦的人来电
Hey Rach, a guy from Ralph Lauren called,
要你去第二关面试
you got a second interview!
我的天  不敢相信我还能去第二关面试
Oh my god. I can't believe it! I got a second interview!
我看那一吻没那么糟嘛
I bet that kiss isn't looking like such a big mistake now, is it?
慢着
What-what, wait a minute,
他要我回去面试不是因为那一吻吧
you don't think that's why he wants me back?
是啊
Yeah!
不是
No?
你们在说什么吻啊
A kiss? What are you talking about?
我意外地在面试中亲了面试官
I accidentally kissed him in the interview,
现在他要我回去复试  当然了
and now he wants me back y'know of course,
"叫那个逢人便亲的女孩回来吧"
'cause "Let's bring back the girl kisses everybody!"
瑞秋  你别乱想了
Come on, Rach.
天哪  万一他觉得我是那种
Oh my God! What if he thinks I'm the kind of girl
随便会跟他上床的人怎么办
that-that would just sleep with him?
他要你复试  或许是因为你适合那工作
He probably wants you back because you're right for the job.
或许吧  我不知道
Maybe. I-I don't know-
天啊  我怎么会那么蠢
Oh God, how could I be so stupid?!
瑞秋  快别那样说了
Oh Rachel look, don't say that,
乔伊给你个抱抱就好
I think you just need a hug from Joey.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
她回来了  辣妹回来了
She's back! Hot girl's back!
还没完全恢复  但是谢谢你
Ohh, well I'm not totally back yet, but thank you.
不是说你  是罗斯那栋楼的辣妹回来了
No, in Ross's building! She's back! She's back!
等一下  我马上过去
Okay, wait there, I'll be over in a second.
一二三  知道了
One two three, got it!
我来看看她有多漂亮
I gotta check out this hot girl!
辣妹在这里
There she is!
可恶  你搬家了吗
Damnit!! Did you move?!
是啊  我跟你们住了一阵子
Yes. I lived with you guys for a while
然后搬到了这里
and then I found this place.
我是罗斯
I'm Ross.
什么事
Yes?
你家里有住辣妹吗
Uhh do you happen to have a hot girl in there?
没有  我一个人住
No. I'm all alone.
是啊  我很遗憾
Yeah. Sorry about that.
小女孩  你好  你妈妈  或是姐姐
Oh, hey little girl. Uhh, is-is your mommy, or sister,
或是保姆  有没有谁正好是辣妹
or babysitter by any chance a hot girl?
爸爸
Daddy!!
再见
Later!
真要命
Oh man!
辣妹
Hot girl!
Hot girl!!
瑞秋  请进
Hi Rachel! Come on in.
很高兴再次见到你
It's really nice to see you again.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋
Oh Rachel, uhh...
什么
What?
那上面
Just ah...
你说什么
Excuse me?
我来帮你
Here let me...
好了  我知道是怎么回事了
All right, okay-okay, I see, I see what's going on here!
听着  抱歉让你误会了
Now listen, look-look, I'm sorry if I gave you the wrong impression,
但我不是那种会出卖自己的随便的女生
but I am not some hussy who will just sleep around to get ahead!
听我说  虽然我亲过你
Now even though I , hey-hey-hey, even though I kissed you,
你也没有权利要我跟你上床
that does not give you the right to demand sex from me.
这份工作我也没有那么想要  再见先生
I do not want, this job that bad. Good day, sir.
说了你们一定不信
Ugh, you will not believe
拉夫·劳伦的混蛋对我做了什么
what that sleaze-ball from Ralph Lauren did too me!
好吧  太神奇了
Okay-okay that-that's amazing.
你们怎么知道的
How did you know that?
你嘴唇上沾到了墨水
You got ink on your lip.
改天让我拿拿你的枪如何
So what do you say, maybe sometime I hold your gun?
不知道  照理说不能那样
I don't know man, we're really not supposed to do that.
又不会怎样
Oh, what can happen? I mean, would you...
我看答案是不行
Yeah, I'm gonna say no.
菲比  晚餐后要去看电影吗
Phoebe, do you want to go see a movie after dinner tonight?
不行  我们已经有计划了
Oh we can't, we already have plans.
你们要去干嘛
What are you doing?
就跟每天一样啊
Well, same thing we did all day,
腻在盖瑞的公寓里
hang out at Gary's apartment.
他好厉害  我们没离开过卧房
He is so amazing, we never left the bedroom.
祝你们看电影愉快
But have fun at the movie.
我们不是要去看电影
Oh, we're not seeing a movie!
那你干嘛问我们要不要去
You're not? Then why did you ask us if we wanted to go?
因为我想知道你有什么安排
Oh umm, that's because I just wanted to what you guys doing
我是怕你不小心冲进我房间
y'know you wouldn't walk in on me and Chandler while we were,
因为我和钱德勒会做上一整晚
y'know, doing it all night.
失陪一下
Will you excuse me for just a second?
钱德勒  方便私下说几句话吗
Chandler? Can I see you for a second?
好
Yeah.
我们一定要打败他们
We have got to beat them!
为什么
Why?
因为盖瑞和菲比  觉得他们比我们更恩爱
'Cause, Gary and Phoebe think they're a hotter couple than we are!
所以呢
Ohh, so?
所以我们要上楼去大干一场
So! So we've got to go upstairs
证明他们是错的
and have a lot of sex to prove them wrong!
莫妮卡  你别再比来比去的
Monica, you have got to stop this competitive thing!
太离谱了
Okay? It's crazy.
只为了让他们见识下我们有多恩爱
I mean, just impress Gary and Phoebe you want me to go upstairs
就要上楼大战数十回合
and have sex with you over and over
我为什么不同意呢  快去拿外套
and I'm saying no to this, why? Get your coat.
借过
Excuse me.
你们应该看一看  通知下其他的住户
You should check this out, tell the other tenants.
这家伙一直在找什么辣妹
Apparently he's running around looking for some kind of a hot girl.
谁不是呢
Who isn't?
初次见面  我是罗斯
I don't, I don't think we've meet. I-I'm Ross.
我知道  你就是那个不愿意交杂工感谢金的人
I know. You're the guy who wouldn't chip in for the handyman.
算了
Never mind!
其实我觉得大家的反应不公平
No, I-I actually thought it was unfair the way everyone reacted.
你才刚搬进来而已
I mean you had just moved in.
我的确是刚搬进来  谢谢
I had just moved in. Thank you!
听我说
Listen umm...
我是珍
Jen.
珍  这听来可能有点...
Jen, I know this may sound a little...
你愿意改天一起喝杯咖啡吗
But uh, would you maybe wanna grab a cup of coffee sometime, or...
当然  我很乐意
Sure! That would be nice.
上面有我的电话  打给我
Oh! My number is on there. Give me a call.
我一定打
I will give you a call.
-回见了  -好
- I'll see you later. - Okay!
我忘了拿报纸
I forgot my paper.
刚才真是太棒了
That was amazing!
等到晚餐时  我一定要说给菲比和盖瑞听
Phoebe and Gary are so gonna hear about this at dinner.
刚才真是太棒了
That was amazing.
我们才是热恋第一名
We are the hottest! Huh?
没人比我们更热恋  我们是最棒的
No one is hotter than we are! We're the best.
你是最棒的
No, you're the best.
不  最棒的是你
不  你才是
No, you're the best.
我是最棒的
I am the best.
两位  你们刚才在干嘛啊
Hey guys!  What'cha been doin'?
乔伊  那不是前几天跟你挥手的女孩吗
Hey Joey! Isn't that the girl that waved at you the other day?
不知道  但你的床单是透明的
I don't know. But I can see through your sheet.
对  是她没错
Yeah, yeah, that's her.
不过算了吧
But y'know what? Doesn't matter,
我无缘跟她见面
I'm never gonna get to meet her anyway.
为什么
Why?
因为我找不到她的公寓
Because it's impossible to find her apartment!
她就像是住在辣妹平行空间里
She lives in some like of hot girl parallel universe, or something.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
她明明就住在二楼
She obviously lives on the second floor,
左边数过来第七间
seventh apartment from the left!
不对
No. No. No.
她住在三楼左边数过来第八间
She lives on the third floor, eighth apartment from the left.
才怪  前两个窗户是大厅的
No, those first two windows,  that's the lobby.
过去那边的是楼梯间窗户
And y'know the other one over there, that's the stairway.
你数错了
You've been counting wrong.
我之前不知道  莫妮卡  多谢
I did not know that! Thank you Monica.
不敢相信我因为数数  差点又失去了一个女孩
I can't believe I almost lost another girl because of counting.
你好了吗
So uhh, you ready?
-好了  我去拿外套  －好
- Sure, I'll just get my coat. - Okay.
你能帮我应门吗
Could you get that?
没问题
Sure.
乔伊
Joey...
不  不
No! Noooo!!
首先我要谢谢你
Ah, first, I-I would like to say thank you
同意再次见我
for agreeing to see me again.
不要紧  但我有义务告诉你
That's quite all right, but I feel obligated to tell you
这次的面试有录影存证
that this meeting is being videotaped.
好  首先我要向你道歉
Okay. Umm, well, first I would like to start by apologizing
我亲了你  还对你大吼
for kissing you and uh, for yelling at you.
好的
Fair enough.
你或许会想雇用
Now you're probably going to hire one of the people
不曾  不曾...
who did not ah,  who did, who did not umm,
对你大吼然后夺门而出的人
yell at you and storm out,
不过那样可就错大了  原因是这样的
and I think that's a big mistake and here's why.
我大出洋相之后还敢回来
I made a huge fool of myself and I came back,
这显示我有勇气
that shows courage.
我以为你要我用性爱来交换工作时
When I thought you wanted sex in exchange for this job,
我拒绝了
I said no.
这表示我有骨气
That shows integrity.
我不害怕挺身为自己辩护
And, I was not afraid to stand up for myself
这表示我有勇气
and that shows courage.
我知道我已经说过勇气了
Okay umm, now I know I already said courage,
不过勇气总是多多益善嘛
but y'know you gotta have courage.
最后当我以为你想趁工作之便
And umm, and finally when I thought you were making
占我便宜时
sexual advances in the workplace,
我拒绝了  但是没打算告你
I said no and I was not litigious.
所以你看  我有勇气  有骨气
So there you go, you got, you got  courage, you got integrity,
双重勇气  而且又不告你
you got courage again, and not litigious.
听我说
Look Mr...
塞纳
Zelner.
塞纳先生  对  我知道
Zelner! Right! I knew that!
我知道
I knew that!
我真的很想要这份工作
I really, really want this job
我想我一定会做得很好
and I think, I think I would be really good at it.
你知道吗
Y'know what?
虽然我可能会后悔
I may regret this but uh,
但我会让你试试看
I'm going to give you a shot.
是吗
Oh! You are?
真的吗  谢谢你
Really? Oh thank you!
我现在抱你是不是很不合适
Oh... Oh, would it be completely inappropriate to give you a hug?
是的
Yes.
那就握手吧
Okay, well then how about a handshake?
天啊  对不起
Oh God I'm sorry!
对不起  我不是故意碰那里的
Oh God, I'm sorry! I did not mean to touch that-
我是说你  那里
I mean you there. There.
好了  谢谢你  我先走了
Uhh, okay, so thank-thank you, I'm going to leave now
非常感谢  谢谢
thank you very much uh-huh, thank you so-
那就星期一见啦
Hey! I'll see you Monday!
钱德勒  你累了吗
You tired Chandler?
今天疯成那样  他不累才怪
You better believe he's tired, after the day we had!
如果你们懂的话  你们懂吧
If you know what I mean. You know what I mean?
亲爱的  连玉米脆片都懂
Honey, the tortilla chips know what you mean.
钱德勒  我给你的警徽喜欢吗
So uh Chandler, do you like that badge I got you?
喜欢  好酷
Oh yeah, it's so cool.
宾警官要先行告退  执行10-100任务
Now I gotta go, Officer Bing has gotta, 10-100.
去尿尿
That's pee-pee.
菲比  你头发里有树枝
Phoebe, you have a, a twig in your hair.
来这里的路上我们绕了一点路
Ohh,  umm, we kinda took a little detour on the way over here.
对  我们去公园里散步
Yeah, we took a little stroll in the park
看四下无人就...
and no one was around, so...
不会吧
You didn't!
我们做了
We did!
我们违反了刑法第12条第7节
We violated Section 12 Paragraph 7 of the criminal code!
在公园是吧
The park huh?
公共场所
A public place.
收到  失陪一下
I hear ya. Excuse me for just a second!
钱德勒
Hi Chandler.
莫妮卡  这是男厕
Monica! This is the Men's room!
没错吧
Isn't it?
没错
Yes it is.
我一直都觉得男厕很性感
You see I've always found the men's bathroom very sexual.
你不觉得吗
Haven't you?
不觉得  否则我们就不会在一起了
No. And if I did, I don't think we'd be going out.
拜托  这越来越离谱了
Come on, this is getting ridiculous!
别这样  我们不能让他们赢
Come on, we can't let them win!
我们已经证明我们在热恋了
Ugh, we have already proved that we are hot! Okay?
为何你走火入魔成这样
So why-why are you getting so obsessed about this thing?!
因为菲比和盖瑞正处在
Because Phoebe and Gary are in that
"难分难舍在公园里做那档事"的阶段
-can't-keep-their-hands-off-each-other-doing-it-in-the-park phase!
所以呢
So?
所以我很伤心  我们不在那个阶段了
So, I feel really sad that we're not...really there anymore.
原来是为了这个
Oh wow! Is that what this all have been about?
我们成天腻在一起时
Wasn't it a lot more exciting when we were y'know
不是更让人激动吗
all over each other all the time?
那时是很棒  真的很棒
Yeah that was great. That was really great!
但是老实跟你说
But to tell you the truth,
我们现在的状况更让我激动
I'm more excited about where we are right now.
真的
Really?
是啊
Yeah!
我从没谈过这么久的恋爱
I've never been in a relationship that's lasted this long before.
过了刚开始的激情期
Y'know to get past the beginning
还一直跟对方在一起
and still be around each other all the time,
我觉得太不可思议了
I think that's pretty incredible.
而且还是和你在一起
And the fact that this is happening all with you,
这让我很激动
yeah I think that's pretty exciting.
你真贴心
That is so sweet.
我知道我表现得有点过火  但是
I know that I was acting a little crazy but umm,
我的感觉跟你一样
I feel the same way.
知道我刚意识到什么吗
Y'know what I just realized?
我们的关系把你吓坏了
You just freaked out about our relationship.
才没有
Did not.
就是有  承认吧  你吓坏了
Yes you did! Admit it! You freaked out!
好吧  我是有一点被吓坏了
Okay, I freaked out a little.
岂止有一点  你被大大地吓坏了
Little?! You freaked out big time! Okay?
我安抚了你  我们角色互换了
And I fixed it! We have switched places!
我现在是恋爱专家
I am the relationship king
而你是疯狂的荒谬的搞砸专家
and you are the crazy, irrational screw up!
现在又回到原位了
And now we're back.
没想到罗斯还真的相信了
I cannot believe Ross is buying this!
谢天谢地  我再也看不下去了
Thank God! I can't watch him anymore!
-你们准备好去看电影没  -好了
- You guys ready fore the movies? - Yeah!
对了  多谢你把帕梅拉和雅丝敏借给我们
Oh by the way, thank you for loaning us Pamela and Yasmine.
要命  她们还真是看不腻
Man! They cannot get enough!